coresense.com 2017-02-15

# CORESense Privacy Policy

## One Application, One Database, One Vendor

At CORESense, we respect the privacy of visitors to our website. This statement describes how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site, www.coresense.com. Collection of Personal Information We may ask for personal information including name, company name, telephone number, and email address when you request a document, signup for a webinar, view a demo, take a survey or engage in some other activity on our site.   
We keep all personal information collected from you at this site strictly confidential and do not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise share your personal information with third parties for their promotional or other uses.   
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure, therefore, we cannot ensure the security of any information you send to us and you do so at your own risk.   
When you visit our Web site, our web server automatically tracks the domain from which you accessed our site and what pages you accessed. This data is used to administer the site, provide general statistics regarding the use of coresense.com and to track the activities of individuals, who have voluntarily provided their personal information, on our site.   
Our Web site may provide links to third party sites. We do not review or control these sites and therefore suggest that you review the privacy policies of such sites.  Use of Personal Information We will use the personal information you give us to provide the information or services you request from us. This may include sending information that you have requested, or contacting you about products and services that you are interested in. If you do not opt-out of communications from CORESense, we may, from time to time, send you marketing notices including promotions of our products and services. You can opt-out of communications from CORESense at any time (see "Control of Personal Information" below)Opting-Out of Communication If you want to opt-out of communications from the company, you can do so by selecign the opt-out link including in all CORESense correspondence, by emailing your request to [info@coresense.com](mailto:info@coresense.com) or by calling us at (866) 229-2804. If you change your mind, you can opt-in again, by emailing this same address. Contact Information  We welcome your input on our privacy policy. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@coresense.com](mailto:info@coresense.com).   
CORESense, Inc.  
ATTN: Marketing  
125 High Rock Ave  
Saratoga Springs, NY 12866 USA   
+1 (866) 229-2805 

"I was impressed at how CORESense was everything we needed in one solution. It wasn't necessary to piece together our business with software X doing this function, and software Y doing this other function." 

"CORESense provides the tools, expertise and best practices to help us succeed. They are an amazing company and two steps ahead of the market with their features and functionality." 

Trophies2Go.com
